Step 1: drag (300, 300) [OK]\NI can see a Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas in the center-left area. The canvas appears to be a rectangul
Step 2: drag (525, 375) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There's already a small diagonal line vis
Step 3: click (1042, 198) [OK]\NI can see a dialog box with 'Leave site?' message is currently open, blocking the canvas. The dialog states 'Changes you
Step 4: drag (225, 420) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There's already a diagonal line drawn on
Step 5: drag (525, 375) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already two diagonal lines draw
Step 6: drag (270, 270) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already several black lines dra
Step 7: drag (525, 300) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already several black diagonal
Step 8: drag (225, 300) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already several black diagonal
Step 9: drag (225, 300) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already several diagonal lines
Step 10: click (1132, 234) [OK]\NI can see a 'Leave site?' dialog box is currently open in the center of the screen, blocking the canvas. The dialog has
Step 11: drag (225, 375) [OK]\NI can see the Kleki Paint Tool interface with a white canvas on the left side. There are already several diagonal lines
Step 12: fail  [FAIL]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see this is a typing test website (typingtest.com), not the Kleki Paint Tool in